<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="tnc_title">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="tnc_desc1">This mobile application NoQ (the “App”) is made available by RadiateLabs, a company limited by guarantee and registered in Kanpur, Uttar Pradesh,
        India and with registered address 3/166 Vishnu Puri, Kanpur, India 208002 (“RadiateLabs”, “us”, “we” or “our”).\nThe terms "We" / "Us" / "Our"/”Company” individually and collectively refer to RadiateLabs and the terms "Visitor” ”User” refer to the users.\nThis page states the Terms and Conditions under which you (Visitor) may visit our App (“NoQ”). Please read this page carefully.
        If you do not accept the Terms and Conditionsstated here, we would request you to exit our App. The business, any of its business divisions and / or its subsidiaries, associate companies or subsidiaries to subsidiaries or
        such other investment companies (in India or abroad) reserve their respective rights to revise these Terms and Conditions at any time by updating this posting. You should visit this
        page periodically to re-appraise yourself of the Terms and Conditions, because they are binding on all users of this App.\nYou, the user of the App, confirm your acceptance of these App terms of use (“App Terms”). If you do not agree to these App Terms, you must immediately
        uninstall the App and discontinue its use. These App Terms should be read alongside our Privacy Policy.</string>

    <string name="tnc_h1">General Terms</string>

    <string name="tnc_sh1_1">App and Related Terms</string>
    <string name="tnc_sh1_1_desc_1">Depending on the version of the Application you have downloaded, these App Terms incorporate Apple’s or Google Android’s terms and conditions and
        privacy policies (“Platform Terms”).If there is any conflict between these App Terms and the Platform Terms then these App Terms will prevail.\nWe may from time to time vary these App Terms. Please check these App Terms regularly to ensure you are aware of any variations made by us.
        If you continue to use this App, you are deemed to have accepted such variations. If you do not agree to such variations, you should not use the App.</string>

    <string name="tnc_sh1_2">Use of the App</string>
    <string name="tnc_sh1_2_desc1">You must be at least 18 years of age and resident in the INDIA to use the App.\nRadiateLabs hereby grants you a non-exclusive, non-transferable, revocable licence to use the App for your personal, non-commercial use and
        only on an Apple or Android device (“Device”)as permitted by the applicable Platform Terms and in accordance with these App Terms (“User Licence”).All other rights in the App are reserved by RadiateLabs.\nIn the
        event of your breach of these App Terms we will be entitled to terminate the User Licence immediately.\nYou acknowledge that your agreement with your mobile network provider (“Mobile Provider”) will apply to your use of the App.
        You acknowledge that you may be charged by the Mobile Provider for data services while using certain features of the App or any such third party charges as
        may arise and you accept responsibility for such charges. If you are not the bill payer for the Device being used to access the App, you will be assumed to
        have received permission from the bill payer for using the App.\nYou acknowledge that where you use services provided by Apple or Google (or any other third parties) in connection with your use
        of the App, you will be subject to Apple’s, Google’s (or the applicable third party’s) terms and conditions and privacy policy and you should ensure that you have read such terms.</string>

    <string name="tnc_sh1_3">Intellectual Property</string>
    <string name="tnc_sh1_3_desc1">The RadiateLabs name and logo, and other RadiateLabs Trust trademarks, service marks, graphics and logos used in connection with the App are trademarks of
        RadiateLabs(collectively “RadiateLabs Trademarks”).  Other trademarks, service marks, graphics and logos used in connection with the App are the trademarks of their respective owners
        (collectively “Third Party Trademarks”).The RadiateLabs Trademarks and Third Party Trademarks may not be copied, imitated or used, in whole or in part, without the prior written
        permission of RadiateLabs or the applicable trademark holder.The App and the content featured in the App are protected by copyright, trademark, patent and other intellectual property
        and proprietary rights which are reserved to RadiateLabs and its licensors.</string>

    <string name="tnc_sh1_4">Prohibited Uses</string>
    <string name="tnc_sh1_4_desc1">You agree not to use the App in any way that:
        <li>is unlawful, illegal or unauthorised;</li>\n
        <li>is defamatory of any other person;</li>\n
        <li>is obscene or offensive;</li>\n
        <li>promotes discrimination based on race, sex, religion, nationality, disability, sexual orientation or age;</li>\n
        <li>infringes any copyright, database right or trade mark of any other person;</li>\n
        <li>is likely to harass, upset, embarrass, alarm or annoy any other person;</li>\n
        <li>is likely to disrupt our service in any way; or</li>\n
        <li>advocates, promotes or assists any unlawful act such as (by way of example only) copyright infringement or computer misuse.</li>
    </string>

    <string name="tnc_sh1_5">Indemnification</string>
    <string name="tnc_sh1_5_desc">You agree to indemnify RadiateLabs for any breach of these App Terms. RadiateLabs reserves the right to control the defence and settlement
        of any third party claim for which you indemnify RadiateLabs under these App Terms and you will assist us in exercising such rights.</string>

    <string name="tnc_sh1_6">No Promises</string>
    <string name="thc_sh1_6_desc1">RadiateLabs provides the App on an ‘as is’ and ‘as available’ basis without any promises or representations, express or implied. In particular,
        RadiateLabs does not warrant or make any representation regarding the validity, accuracy, reliability or availability of the App or its content. All product details, prices
        and related information is based on information provided by retailers and such data, and other content on the App, may be out of date and RadiateLabs makes no commitment to update it.\nTo the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, RadiateLabs hereby excludes all promises, whether express or implied, including any promises
        that the App is fit for purpose, of satisfactory quality, non-infringing, is free of defects, is able to operate on an uninterrupted basis, that the use of the App by you follows
        laws or that any information that you transmit in connection with this App will be successfully, accurately or securely transmitted.</string>

    <string name="tnc_sh1_7">Reliance on Information</string>
    <string name="tnc_sh1_7_desc">The App is intended to provide general information only and, as such, should not be considered as a substitute for advice covering any specific situation.
        You should seek appropriate advice before taking or refraining from taking any action in reliance on any information contained in the App. </string>


    <string name="tnc_sh1_8">Exclusion of RadiateLabs’ Liability</string>
    <string name="tnc_sh1_8_desc1">Nothing in these App Terms shall exclude or in any way limit RadiateLabs’ liability for death or personal injury caused by its negligence or for fraud
        or any other liability to the extent the same may not be excluded or limited as a matter of law.\nTo the fullest extent permitted under applicable law, in no event shall RadiateLabs be liable to you with respect to use of the App and/or be liable to
        you for any direct, indirect, special or consequential damages including, without limitation, damages for loss of goodwill, lost profits, or loss, theft or corruption of your
        information, the inability to use the App, Device failure or malfunction.\nRadiateLabs shall not be liable even if it has been advised of the possibility of such damages, including without limitation damages caused by error,
        omission, interruption, defect, failure of performance, unauthorised use, delay in operation or transmission, line failure, computer virus, worm, Trojan horse or other harm.\nIn the event that applicable law does not allow the exclusion of certain promises and/or the exclusion of liability for direct, indirect, consequential
        or other damages, in no event shall RadiateLabs’ liability arising under or in connection with these App Terms and your use of the App exceed Rs. 1000.</string>

    <string name="tnc_sh1_9">General</string>
    <string name="tnc_sh1_9_desc1">These App Terms shall be governed by the laws of Kanpur, Uttar Pradesh, India and the parties submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of Kanpur,
        Uttar Pradesh, India to resolve any dispute between them arising under or in connection with these App Terms.\nIf any provision (or part of a provision) of these App Terms is found by any court or administrative body of competent jurisdiction to be invalid,
        unenforceable or illegal, such term, condition or provision will to that extent be severed from the remaining terms, conditions and provisions which will continue to be valid
        to the fullest extent permitted by law.</string>

    <string name="tnc_sh1_10">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="tnc_sh1_10_desc">If you have any questions regarding our App, you can email us at noq@radiatelabs.com </string>

</resources>