<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="pp_title">Privacy Policy </string>
    <string name="pp_date">Effective Date: 06/30/2019</string>
    <string name="pp_desc">Applicable To The Following Mobile Application:</string>

    <string name="pp_main_title">NoQ</string>
    <string name="pp_desc1">The terms "We" / "Us" / "Our"/”Company” individually and collectively refer to RadiateLabs and the terms "You" /"Your" / "Yourself" refer to the users. </string>
    <string name="pp_desc2">This Privacy Policy is an electronic record in the form of an electronic contract formed under the information Technology Act, 2000 and the rules made
        thereunder and the amended provisions pertaining to electronic documents / records in various statutes as amended by the information Technology Act, 2000. This Privacy
        Policy does not require any physical, electronic or digital signature.</string>
    <string name="pp_desc3">This Privacy Policy is a legally binding document between you and RadiateLabs (both terms defined below). The terms of this Privacy Policy will be
        effective upon your acceptance of the same (directly or indirectly in electronic form, by clicking on the I accept tab or by use of the app or by other means) and will
        govern the relationship between you and RadiateLabs for your use of the App “NoQ” (defined below).</string>
    <string name="pp_desc4">This document is published and shall be construed in accordance with the provisions of the Information Technology (reasonable security practices and
        procedures and sensitive personal data of information) rules, 2011 under Information Technology Act, 2000; that require publishing of the Privacy Policy for collection,
        use, storage and transfer of sensitive personal data or information.</string>
    <string name="pp_desc5">Please read this Privacy Policy carefully by using the App, you indicate that you understand, agree and consent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not
        agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use this App. </string>
    <string name="pp_desc6">By providing us your Information or by making use of the facilities provided by the App, you hereby consent to the collection, storage, processing and
        transfer of any or all of Your Personal Information and Non-Personal Information by us as specified under this Privacy Policy. You further agree that such collection, use,
        storage and transfer of Your Information shall not cause any loss or wrongful gain to you or any other person.</string>

    <string name="pp_h1">Article 1 - DEFINITIONS : </string>
    <string name="pp_h1_desc1">a) APPLICABLE MOBILE APPLICATION: This Privacy Policy will refer to and be applicable to the Mobile App listed above, which shall hereinafter be
        referred to as "Mobile App."</string>
    <string name="pp_h1_desc2">b) EFFECTIVE DATE: "Effective Date" means the date this Privacy Policy comes into force and effect.</string>
    <string name="pp_h1_desc3">c) PARTIES: The parties to this privacy policy are the following data controller: RadiateLabs ("Data Controller") and you, as the user of
        this Mobile App. Hereinafter, the parties will individually be referred to as "Party" and collectively as "Parties."</string>
    <string name="pp_h1_desc4">d) DATA CONTROLLER: Data Controller is the publisher, owner, and operator of the Mobile App and is the Party responsible for the collection
        of information described herein. Data Controller shall be referred to either by Data Controller\'s name or "Data Controller," as listed above. If Data Controller
        or Data Controller\'s property shall be referred to through first-person pronouns, it shall be through the use of the following: us, we, our, ours, etc.</string>
    <string name="pp_h1_desc5">e) YOU: Should you agree to this Privacy Policy and continue your use of the Mobile App, you will be referred to herein as either you, the
        user, or if any second-person pronouns are required and applicable, such pronouns as \'your", "yours", etc.</string>
    <string name="pp_h1_desc6">f) GOODS: "Goods" means any goods that we make available for sale on the Mobile App.</string>
    <string name="pp_h1_desc7">g) PERSONAL DATA: "Personal DATA" means personal data and information that we obtain from you in connection with your use of the Mobile
        App which is capable of identifying you in any manner.</string>

    <string name="pp_h2">Article 2 - GENERAL INFORMATION : </string>
    <string name="pp_h2_desc1">This privacy policy (hereinafter "Privacy Policy") describes how we collect and use the Personal Data that we receive about you,
        as well as your rights in relation to that Personal Data, when you visit our Mobile App or purchase our Goods.</string>
    <string name="pp_h2_desc2">This Privacy Policy does not cover any information that we may receive about you through sources other than the use of our Mobile App.
        The Mobile App may link out to other websites or mobile applications, but this Privacy Policy does not and will not apply to any of those linked websites or applications.</string>
    <string name="pp_h2_desc3">We are committed to the protection of your privacy while you use our Mobile App.</string>
    <string name="pp_h2_desc4">By continuing to use our Mobile App, you acknowledge that you have had the chance to review and consider this Privacy Policy, and you acknowledge that you agree to it.
        This means that you also consent to the use of your information and the method of disclosure as described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not understand the Privacy Policy or do
        not agree to it then you agree to immediately cease your use of our Mobile App.</string>

    <string name="pp_h3">Article 3 -CONTACT AND DATA PROTECTION OFFICER : </string>
    <string name="pp_h3_desc1">The Party responsible for the processing of your personal data is as follows: RadiateLabs. The Data Controller may be contacted as follows:</string>
    <string name="pp_h3_emai1l">noq@radiatelabs.com</string>
    <string name="pp_h3_web">https://www.radiatelabs.com</string>
    <string name="pp_h3_desc2">The Data Controller and operator of the Mobile App are one and the same.</string>
    <string name="pp_h3_desc3">The Data Protection Officer is as follows: Amit Gupta. The Data Protection Officer may be contacted as follows:</string>
    <string name="pp_h3_email2">amit@radiatelabs.com</string>

    <string name="pp_h4">Article 4 - LOCATION : </string>
    <string name="pp_h4_desc1">The location where the data processing activities take place is as follows:
    India</string>

    <string name="pp_h5">Article 5 - MODIFICATIONS AND REVISIONS : </string>
    <string name="pp_h5_desc">We reserve the right to modify, revise, or otherwise amend this Privacy Policy at any time and in any manner.
        If we do so, however, we will notify you and obtain your consent to the change in processing. Unless we specifically obtain your consent,
        any changes to the Privacy Policy will only impact the information collected on or after the date of the change. It is also your responsibility
        to periodically check this page for any such modification, revision or amendment.</string>

    <string name="pp_h6">Article 6 - THE PERSONAL DATA WE RECEIVE FROM YOU : </string>
    <string name="pp_h6_desc">Depending on how you use our Mobile App, you will be subject to different types of Personal Data collected and different manners of collection:</string>
    <string name="pp_h6_sh1">a) Registered users: </string>
    <string name="pp_h6_sh1_desc1">You, as a user of the Mobile App, may be asked to register in order to use the Mobile App or to purchase the Goods available for sale.</string>
    <string name="pp_h6_sh1_desc2">During the process of your registration, we will collect some of the following Personal Data from you through your voluntary disclosure:</string>
    <string name="pp_h6_sh1_desc3">Name, Phone Number, Email Address
        Personal Data may be asked for in relation to:</string>
    <string name="pp_h6_sh1_desc4">
        I) Interaction with our representatives in any way \n
        II) making purchases \n
        III) receiving notifications by text message or email about marketing \n
        IV) receiving general emails from us \n
        V) commenting on our content or other user-generated content on our Mobile App, such as blogs, articles, photographs or videos, or participating in our forums, bulletin boards, chat rooms or other similar features \n
        VI) Or the following other forms of participation: \n
                Feedback, Rating \n
        By undergoing the registration process, you consent to us collecting your Personal Data, including the Personal Data described in this clause, as well as storing,
        using or disclosing your Personal Data in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
    </string>
    <string name="pp_h6_sh2">b) Unregistered users : </string>
    <string name="pp_h6_sh2_desc">If you are a passive user of the Mobile App and do not register for any purchases or other service, you may still be subject to certain passive data collection ("Passive Data Collection").
        Such Passive Data Collection may include through cookies, as described below, IP address information, location information, and certain browser data, such as history and/or session information.</string>

    <string name="pp_h6_sh3">c) All users : </string>
    <string name="pp_h6_sh3_desc">The Passive Data Collection which applies to Unregistered users shall also apply to all other users and/or visitors of our Mobile App.</string>

    <string name="pp_h6_sh4">d) Sales &amp; Billing Information : </string>
    <string name="pp_h6_sh4_desc">In order to purchase any of the goods on the Mobile App, you will be asked to provide certain credit information, billing address information, and possibly additional specific
        information so that you may be properly charged for your purchases. This payment and billing information will not be stored and will be used exclusively to assist with your one-time purchase.</string>

    <string name="pp_h6_sh5">e) Related Entities : </string>
    <string name="pp_h6_sh5_desc1">We may share your Personal Data, including Personal Data that identifies you personally, with any of our parent companies, subsidiary companies, affiliates or other trusted
        related entities.</string>
    <string name="pp_h6_sh5_desc2">However, we only share your Personal Data with a trusted related entity if that entity agrees to our privacy standards as set out in this Privacy Policy and to treat your
        Personal Data in the same manner that we do.</string>

    <string name="pp_h6_sh6">f) Email Marketing : </string>
    <string name="pp_h6_sh6_desc">You may be asked to provide certain Personal Data, such as your name and email address, for the purpose of receiving email marketing communications.
        This information will only be obtained through your voluntary disclosure and you will be asked to affirmatively opt-in to email marketing communications.</string>

    <string name="pp_h6_sh7">g) User Experience : </string>
    <string name="pp_h6_sh7_desc">From time to time we may request information from you to assist us in improving our Mobile App, and the Goods we sell, such as demographic information
        or your particular preferences.</string>

    <string name="pp_h6_sh8">h) Content Interaction : </string>
    <string name="pp_h6_sh8_desc">Our Mobile App may allow you to comment on the content that we provide or the content that other users provide, such as blogs, multimedia, or forum posts.
        If so, we may collect some Personal Data from you at that time, such as, but not limited to, username or email address.</string>

    <string name="pp_h6_sh9">i) Combined or Aggregated Information : </string>
    <string name="pp_h6_sh9_desc1">We may combine or aggregate some of your Personal Data in order to better serve you and to better enhance and update our Mobile App for your and other consumers\' use.</string>
    <string name="pp_h6_sh9_desc2">We may also share such aggregated information with others, but only if that aggregated information does not contain any Personal Data.</string>

    <string name="pp_h6_sh10">j) Other Information : </string>
    <string name="pp_h6_sh10_desc">In addition to collecting the Personal Data as already described herein, we may also collect the following Personal Data:
        Purchases made by the Customer</string>

    <string name="pp_h7">Article 7 - THE PERSONAL DATA WE RECEIVE AUTOMATICALLY:</string>
    <string name="pp_h7_sh1">Cookies : </string>
    <string name="pp_h7_sh1_desc1">We may collect information from you through automatic tracking systems (such as information about your browsing preferences) as well as through information that you
        volunteer to us (such as information that you provide during a registration process or at other times while using the Mobile App, as described above).</string>
    <string name="pp_h7_sh1_desc2">For example, we use cookies to make your browsing experience easier and more intuitive: cookies are small strings of text used to store some information that may
        concern the user, his or her preferences or the device they are using to access the Internet (such as a computer, tablet, or mobile phone). Cookies are mainly used to adapt the operation of
        the site to your expectations, offering a more personalized browsing experience and memorizing the choices you made previously.</string>
    <string name="pp_h7_sh1_desc3">A cookie consists of a reduced set of data transferred to your browser from a web server and it can only be read by the server that made the transfer.
        This is not executable code and does not transmit viruses.</string>
    <string name="pp_h7_sh1_desc4">Cookies do not record or store any Personal Data. If you want, you can prevent the use of cookies, but then you may not be able to use our Mobile App as we intend.
        To proceed without changing the options related to cookies, simply continue to use our Mobile App.</string>
    <string name="pp_h7_sh1_1">Technical cookies : </string>
    <string name="pp_h7_sh1_1_desc1">Technical cookies, which can also sometimes be called HTML cookies, are used for navigation and to facilitate your access to and use of the site. They are necessary
        for the transmission of communications on the network or to supply services requested by you. The use of technical cookies allows the safe and efficient use of the site.</string>
    <string name="pp_h7_sh1_1_desc2">You can manage or request the general deactivation or cancelation of cookies through your browser. If you do this though, please be advised this action
        might slow down or prevent access to some parts of the site.</string>
    <string name="pp_h7_sh1_1_desc3">Cookies may also be retransmitted by an analytics or statistics provider to collect aggregated information on the number of users and how they visit the Mobile App.
        These are also considered technical cookies when they operate as described.</string>
    <string name="pp_h7_sh1_1_desc4">Temporary session cookies are deleted automatically at the end of the browsing session - these are mostly used to identify you and ensure that you don\'t
        have to log in each time - whereas permanent cookies remain active longer than just one particular session.</string>
    <string name="pp_h7_sh1_2">Third-party cookies : </string>
    <string name="pp_h7_sh1_2_desc1">We may also utilize third-party cookies, which are cookies sent by a third-party to your computer. Permanent cookies are often third-party cookies.
        The majority of third-party cookies consist of tracking cookies used to identify online behavior, understand interests and then customize advertising for users.</string>
    <string name="pp_h7_sh1_2_desc2">Third-party analytical cookies may also be installed. They are sent from the domains of the aforementioned third parties external to the site.
        Third-party analytical cookies are used to detect information on user behavior on our Mobile App. This place anonymously, in order to monitor the performance and improve
        the usability of the site. Third-party profiling cookies are used to create profiles relating to users, in order to propose advertising in line with the choices expressed
        by the users themselves.</string>

    <string name="pp_h7_sh1_2_desc3">Profiling cookies: We may also use profiling cookies, which are those that create profiles related to the user and are used in order to send
        advertising to the user\'s browser. When these types of cookies are used, we will receive your explicit consent.Support in configuring your browser: You can manage cookie
        through the settings of your browser on your device. However, deleting cookies from your browser may remove the preferences you have set for this Mobile App.
        For further information and support, you can also visit the specific help page of the web browser you are using:
        - Internet Explorer: http://windows.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-vista/block-or-allow-cookies
        - Firefox: https://support.mozilla.org/en-us/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences
        - Safari: http://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/
        - Chrome: https://support.google.com/accounts/answer/61416?hl=en
        - Opera: http://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/cookies/
        Log Data: Like all websites and mobile applications, this Mobile App also makes use of log files which store automatic information collected during user visits.
        The different types of log data could be as follows:
        - internet protocol (IP) address;
        - type of browser and device parameters used to connect to the Mobile App;
        - name of the Internet Service Provider (ISP);
        - date and time of visit;
        - web page of origin of the user (referral) and exit;
        - possibly the number of clicks.
        The aforementioned information is processed in an automated form and collected in an exclusively aggregated manner in order to verify the correct functioning of the site,
        and for security reasons. This information will be processed according to the legitimate interests of the Data Controller For security purposes (spam filters, firewalls,
        virus detection), the automatically recorded data may also possibly include Personal Data such as IP address, which could be used, in accordance with applicable laws, in
        order to block attempts at damage to the Mobile App or damage to other users, or in the case of harmful activities or crime. Such data are never used for the identification
        or profiling of the user, but only for the protection of the Mobile App and our users. Such information will be treated according to the legitimate interests of the Data Controller.
        Article 8 - THIRD PARTIES:
        We may utilize third party service providers ("Third Party Service Providers"), from time to time or all the time, to help us with our Mobile App, and to help serve you.
        We may use Third Party Service Providers to assist with information storage (such as cloud storage).
        We may provide some of your Personal Data to Third Party Service Providers in order to help us track usage data, such as referral websites, dates and times of page requests,
        etc. We use this information to understand patterns of usage of, and to improve, the Mobile App.
        We may use Third Party Service Providers to host the Mobile App. In this instance, the Third Party Service Provider will have access to your Personal Data.
        We may use Third Party Service Providers to fulfill orders in relation to the Mobile App.
        We may allow third parties to advertise on the Mobile App. These third parties may use cookies in connection with their advertisements (see the "Cookies" clause in this Privacy Policy).
        The countries or regions in which our Third Party Service Providers may be located include:
        India
        We only share your Personal Data with a Third Party Service Provider if that provider agrees to our privacy standards as set out in this Privacy Policy.
        Your Personal Data will not be sold or otherwise transferred to other third parties without your approval.
        Notwithstanding the other provisions of this Privacy Policy, we may provide your Personal Data to a third party or to third parties in order to protect the rights, property or safety,
        of us, our customers or third parties, or as otherwise required by law.We will not knowingly share your Personal Data with any third parties other than in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
        If your Personal Data might be provided to a third party in a manner which is other than as explained in this Privacy Policy, you will be notified. you will also have the opportunity to request
        that we not share that information.
        Article 9 - HOW PERSONAL DATA IS STORED:
        We use secure physical and digital systems to store your Personal Data when appropriate. We ensure that your Personal Data is protected against unauthorized access, disclosure, or destructions.
        Please note, however, that no system involving the transmission of information via the internet, or the electronic storage of data, is completely secure. However, we take the protection and storage
        of your Personal Data very seriously. We take all reasonable steps to protect your Personal Data.The systems that we use to store your information include but are not limited to:
        Only employees with clearance will be handling the personal information of customer.
        Personal Data is stored throughout your relationship with us. We delete your Personal Data upon request for cancelation of your account or other general request for the deletion of data.
        In the event of a breach of your Personal Data, you will be notified in a reasonable time frame, but in no event later than two weeks, and we will follow all applicable laws regarding such breach.
        Article 10 - PURPOSES OF PROCESSING OF PERSONAL DATA:
        We primarily use your Personal Data to help us provide a better experience for you on our Mobile App and to provide you the services and/or information you may have requested, such as use of our Mobile App.
        Information that does not identify you personally, but that may assist in providing us broad overviews of our customer base, will be used for market research or marketing efforts. Such information may include,
        but is not limited to, interests based on your cookies.
        Personal Data that may be considering identifying may be used for the following:
        a) Improving your personal user experience
        b) Communicating with you about your user account with us
        c) Marketing and advertising to you, including via email
        d) Fulfilling your purchases
        e) Providing customer service to you
        f) Advising you about updates to the Mobile App or related Items
        Article 11 - DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL DATA:
        Although our policy is to maintain the privacy of your Personal Data as described herein, we may disclose your Personal Data if we believe that it is reasonable to do so in certain cases, in our sole and exclusive
        discretion. Such cases may include, but are not limited to:
        a) To satisfy any local, state, or Federal laws or regulations
        b) To respond to requests, such discovery, criminal, civil, or administrative process, subpoenas, court orders, or writs from law enforcement or other governmental or legal bodies
        c) To bring legal action against a user who has violated the law or violated the terms of use of our Mobile App
        d) As may be necessary for the operation of our Mobile App
        e) To generally cooperate with any lawful investigation about our users
        f) If we suspect any fraudulent activity on our Mobile App or if we have noticed any activity which may violate our terms or other applicable rules
        Article 12 - OPTING OUT OF TRANSMITTALS FROM US:
        From time to time, we may send you informational or marketing communications related to our Mobile App such as announcements or other information. If you wish to opt-out of such communications, you may contact the
        following email: noq@radiatelabs.com. You may also click the opt-out link which will be provided at the bottom of any and all such communications.Please be advised that even though you may opt-out of such communications,
        you may still receive information from us that is specifically about your use of our Mobile App or about your account with us.By providing any Personal Data to us, or by using our Mobile App in any manner, you have created
        a commercial relationship with us. As such, you agree that any email sent from us or third-party affiliates, even unsolicited email, shall specifically not be considered SPAM, as that term is legally defined.
        Article 13 - MODIFYING, DELETING, AND ACCESSING YOUR INFORMATION:
        If you wish to modify or delete any information we may have about you, or you wish to simply access any information we have about you, you may do so from your account settings page.
        Article 14 - ACCEPTANCE OF RISK:
        By continuing to our Mobile App in any manner, use the Product, you manifest your continuing asset to this Privacy Policy. You further acknowledge, agree and accept that no transmission of information or data via
        the internet is not always completely secure, no matter what steps are taken. You acknowledge, agree and accept that we do not guarantee or warrant the security of any information that you provide to us, and that
        you transmit such information at your own risk.
        Article 15 - YOUR RIGHTS:
        You have many rights in relation to your Personal Data. Specifically, your rights are as follows:
        - the right to be informed about the processing of your Personal Dat
        - the right to have access to your Personal Data
        - the right to update and/or correct your Personal Data
        - the right to portability of your Personal Data
        - the right to oppose or limit the processing of your Personal Data
        - the right to request that we stop processing and delete your Personal Data
        - the right to block any Personal Data processing in violation of any applicable law
        - the right to launch a complaint with the Federal Trade Commission (FTC) in the United States or applicable data protection authority in another jurisdiction
        Such rights can all be exercised by contacting us at the relevant contact information listed in this Privacy Policy.
        Article 16 - INFORMATION SECURITY
        We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and
        processing practices and security measures, including appropriate encryption and physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.All information gathered
        on our App is securely stored within our controlled database. The database is stored on servers secured behind a firewall; access to the servers is password-protected and is strictly limited. However, as effective
        as our security measures are, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted
        to us over the Internet. And, of course, any information you include in a posting to the discussion areas is available to anyone with Internet access.
        However, the internet is an ever-evolving medium. We may change our Privacy Policy from time to time to incorporate necessary future changes. Of course, our use of any information we gather will always be consistent
        with the policy under which the information was collected, regardless of what the new policy may be.
        Article 17 - CONTACT INFORMATION:
        If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the way we collect information from you, or if you would like to launch a complaint about anything related to this Privacy Policy, you may contact us at the following email address: noq@radiatelabs.com.



    </string>

</resources>